[{"answer": "Not really, no.", "docId": "110819pmt", "aSentId": 6, "question": "Well, don't you think as a host, if I say this is what I want to talk about, that's what we should address?", "qSentId": 5}, {"answer": "I'm not.", "docId": "110819pmt", "aSentId": 26, "question": "Are we done?", "qSentId": 25}, {"answer": "Not really, no.", "docId": "110819pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "Well, don't you think as a host, if I say this is what I want to talk about, that's what we should address?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "For one thing, after Christine O'Donnell walked off the set, she didn't have to talk much more about the campaign or the book.", "docId": "110819pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "Where are you going?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "Piers, in this instance you are definitely not guilty.", "docId": "110819pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "Am I guilty?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "That was the impression I got as well.", "docId": "110819pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "Did you think that?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "Speaking for all men, I absolve you from sexism on this as well.", "docId": "110819pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "Did you think I was crossing a line?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "I -- I think that's probably -- I think it's probably true, that if you're going out to promote a book you should be willing to talk about the book.", "docId": "110819pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "What do you think, James?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, I do represent probably more sexual harassment victims than any other attorney in the country, and I will say this.", "docId": "110819pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "What's your damning verdict?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "I'm doing well.", "docId": "110819pmt", "aSentId": 183, "question": "Christine O'Donnell, how are you?", "qSentId": 182}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "110819pmt", "aSentId": 201, "question": "You can be both, can't you?", "qSentId": 200}, {"answer": "Well, I think -- I like the way you say it's a hiccup.", "docId": "110819pmt", "aSentId": 213, "question": "When you look back on it, what was the catalyst, do you think, or -- not your downfall but your hiccup?", "qSentId": 212}, {"answer": "Because I dabbled into witchcraft.", "docId": "110819pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "How can you be a witch?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110819pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "Your first date was in the satanic altar?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "Well, I hope to stay in the political arena -- maybe not necessarily as a candidate or in an elected office.", "docId": "110819pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "I would have thought there was a pretty good chance that you can make a pretty big move back into the political stage, isn't it?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110819pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "The problem, Christine, if I may just jump in there?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "Let's not even go there.", "docId": "110819pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "Do you still think masturbation is wrong?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "Well, I am a practicing Catholic and I support what the Catholic Church teaches.", "docId": "110819pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "So, am I right in assuming your views have evolved over the years?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "Let's not even go there.", "docId": "110819pmt", "aSentId": 399, "question": "Can I ask you, have you -- have you committed lust in your heart and therefore adultery?", "qSentId": 398}, {"answer": "I address that stuff in the book.", "docId": "110819pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "-- what is your view of gay marriage, for example?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "-- I obviously want to talk about the issues that I choose to talk about in the book.", "docId": "110819pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "I talk about my religious beliefs, yes.", "docId": "110819pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "Do you answer that question in the book?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "Because I don't think it's relevant.", "docId": "110819pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "So, I'm bemused as to why you wouldn't just say it in an interview if it's in the book?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "I'm not talking policies.", "docId": "110819pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "You should restore that?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "I'm not being weird about this, Piers.", "docId": "110819pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "Why are you being so weird about this?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "Not really, no.", "docId": "110819pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "Well, don't you think as a host, if I say this is what I want to talk about, that's what we should address?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "Well, I was supposed to be speaking at the Republican women's club at 6:00, and I chose to be a little late for that not to be -- you know, yes, not to endure rude talk show hosts, but to talk to you about my book and to talk about the issues that I address in my book.", "docId": "110819pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "You're leaving?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "Yes, but these issues are in your book.", "docId": "110819pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "Have you read the book?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "He's still there.", "docId": "110819pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "Are we done?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "I mean, I thought it was odd that she walked off.", "docId": "110819pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "But when you watched it, what did you think?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "That doesn't sound entirely consistent.", "docId": "110819pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "What do you make of those two comments?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "He appointed me and I stood up and took the appointment to serve my country.", "docId": "110819pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "Do you have sympathy for him in the position he found himself in, where you have such an intransigent part of the Republican party really just refusing to compromise?", "qSentId": 551}]